Preliminary Guide to the Mobius Advertising Awards Collection, [1970s]-2002, bulk 1984-2002 RL.00902
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 1997-051, 1985-1989; 1
  - Maclaren Advertising, "Bowling Ball", :15; Mobius category: 16; Mobius identifier: XT1460-16-0-80-C, 1988 September 06; 46
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0051)
  - Maclaren Advertising, Molson Breweries/Canadian Light, "Wrecker Ball", :15; Mobius category: 16; Mobius identifier: XT1459-16-0-88-C, 1988 September 06; 47
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0061)
  - Maclaren Advertising, Molson Breweries/Canadian, "Outdoors", 30E, "Weekend", 30E, "Ballroom, 30E"; Mobius category: 16; Mobius identifier: XT1461ABC-16-0-88-C, 1988 September 29; 48
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0052)
  - Maclaren Advertising, Molson Breweries/Canadian Light, "Dancing Fool", :30; Mobius category: 16; Mobius identifier: XT1456-16-0-88-C, 1988 September 29; 49
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0060)
  - Maclaren Advertising, Molson Breweries/Canadian Light, "Bellies" :30; Mobius category: 16; Mobius identifier: XT1458-16-0-88-C, 1988 September 29; 50
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0062)
  - Maclaren Advertising, Molson Breweries/Canadian Light, "Weekend" :30; Mobius category: 16; Mobius identifier: XT1463-16-0-88-C, 1988 September 29; 51
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0063)
  - O.V. Beer, "Good Times"; Mobius category: 16; Mobius identifier: XT1413-16-0-88-U, circa 1988; 52
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0053)
  - Sheep, Amstel Brewery Canada Ltd., 1 x :30, Vickers & Benson Advertising Ltd.; Mobius category: 16; Mobius identifier: XT1264-16-0-88-C, circa 1988; 53
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0059)
  - MSD Agvet, Ivomec/Cattle, "New Calves", MKIC-0023; Mobius category: 13; Mobius identifier: XT324-13-0-88-U, circa 1988; 54
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0073)
  - Hanes Hosiery, Inc. "Reflections on Jeanne" :30, CFHM 0193; Mobius category: 12; Mobius identifier: XT370-12-0-88-U, circa 1988; 55
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0074)
  - Daylight Savings; Mobius category: 72; Mobius identifier: XT1491-72-0-88-U, circa 1988; 56
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0075)
  - Masseuse; Mobius category: 21; Mobius identifier: XT1495-21-0-88-U, circa 1988; 57
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0076)
  - Bend Over; Mobius category: 21; Mobius identifier: XT1507-21-0-88-U, circa 1988; 58
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0077)
  - Hanes Hosiery, Inc., "Taxi" :15, CFHM 0205; Mobius category: 12; Mobius identifier: XT369-12-0-88-U, circa 1988; 59
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0078)
  - Hanes Hosiery, Inc., "Rooftop" :15 CFHM 0185; Mobius category: 12; Mobius identifier: XT368-12-0-88-U, circa 1988; 60
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0079)
  - Hanes Hosiery, Inc., "Shoe" :15 CFHM 0175; Mobius category: 12; Mobius identifier: XT367-12-0-88-U, circa 1988; 61
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0080)
  - Daylight Savings; Mobius category: 37; Mobius identifier: XT1506-37-0-88-U, circa 1988; 62
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0081)
  - Speedskater; Mobius category: 37; Mobius identifier: XT1500-37-0-88-U, circa 1988; 63
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0082)
  - Seoul Man; Mobius category: 84; Mobius identifier: XT1501-84-0-88-U, circa 1988; 64
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0083)
  - WHOI-TV Community Image; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT1171-73-U-89-U, 1989; 65
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 32, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0001)
  - TV's Greatest Bloopers, Direct Repsonse Spot; Mobius category: 75; Mobius identifier: XT1153-75-U-89-U, 1989; 66
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0137)
  - KARE-TV, "1989 Winter Carnival Torchlight Parade" :18; Mobius category: 76; Mobius identifier: XT15-76-U-89-U, 1989 February 28; 67
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0140)
  - KARE-TV, "Eleven Who Care" :14; Mobius category: 76; Mobius identifier: XT14-76-U-89-U, 1989 February 28; 68
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0141)
  - Publicite Kitching Voyager, "Laissez Vous Transporter" :30,; Mobius category: 62; Mobius identifier: XT458-62-0-89-C, 1989 July 13; 69
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0072)
  - Client: McDaniel Olds, Buick, Toyota, Inc., Spot: Movin' South, :30; Mobius category: 2; Mobius identifier: XT851-2-U-89-U, circa 1989-08; 70
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0139)
  - Turan Lane Adv., "Metro Prizm", Gerry Lane, :30; Mobius category: 1; Mobius identifier: XT87-1-U-89-U, 1989 August 18; 71
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0124)
  - Clint Hackney, "Dance" :30, Mandate: Campaign Media; Mobius category: 69; Mobius identifier: XT580-69-U-89-U, 1989 September 10; 72
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0132)
  - Ted Lyon: "Pounds" :30, Mandate: Campaign Media; Mobius category: 69; Mobius identifier: XT581-69-U-89-U, 1989 September 10; 73
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0133)
  - Voyageur Bus, "Loon River" Kingston, 1 x 30 sec., Agency: Kitching Adv.; Mobius category: 62; Mobius identifier: XT457-62-0-89-C, 1989 September 12; 74
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0058)
  - Chrysler: Jeep-Eagle, Campbell-Mithun-Esty, AOFX-5115, "Counter Warranty Rev.", :15; Mobius category: 1; Mobius identifier: XT754-1-U-89-U, 1989 September 19; 75
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0110)
  - Chrysler: Jeep-Eagle, Campbell-Mithun-Esty, AOFX-5135, "Brakes", :15; Mobius category: 1; Mobius identifier: XT753-1-U-89-U, 1989 September 19; 76
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0111)
  - Chrysler: Jeep-Eagle, Campbell-Mithun-Esty, AOFX-5295, "Euro Quotes", :15; Mobius category: 1; Mobius identifier: XT748-1-U-89-U, 1989 September 19; 77
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0112)
  - Chrysler: Jeep-Eagle, Campbell-Mithun-Esty, AOFX-5065, "Echo-Without Cut", :15; Mobius category: 1; Mobius identifier: XT749-1-U-89-U, 1989 September 19; 78
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0113)
  - Chrysler: Jeep-Eagle, Campbell-Mithun-Esty, AOFX-5345 "Power Mirrors Rev." :15, AOFX-5345; Mobius category: 1; Mobius identifier: XT751-1-U-89-U, 1989 September 19; 79
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0115)
  - Chrysler: Jeep-Eagle, Campbell-Mithun-Esty, AOFX-5095 "Room All Out Rev." :15; Mobius category: 1; Mobius identifier: XT760-1-U-89-U, 1989 September 19; 80
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0117)
  - Campbell-Mithun-Esty, AOFX-5095 "Room All Out Rev." :15, AOFX-5135 "Brakes" :15, AOFX-5295 "Euro Quotes" :15; Mobius category: 1; Mobius identifier: XT762ABC-1-U-89-U, 1989 September 20; 81
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0114)
  - Campbell-Mithun-Esty, AOFX-5095 "Room All Out Rev." :15, AOFX-5135 "Brakes" :15, AOFX-5305 "Aerodynamics" :15; Mobius category: 1; Mobius identifier: XT750ABC-1-U-89-U, 1989 September 20; 82
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0116)
  - Palmer Bonner BCP, Scholl Plough Correctol, "Hallelujah" :30; Mobius category: 47, 48; Mobius identifier: XT139-48-U-89-C, XT140-47-U-89-C, 1989 September 21; 83
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0119)
  - Father Dowling "Pope"; Net A&P Father Dowling 'Thumbs Up'; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT556-73-U-89-U, 1989 September 22; 84
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 32, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0003)
  - Little Brother :30; Mobius category: 7; Mobius identifier: XT729-7-0-89-C, 1989 September 23; 85
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0108)
  - Bubble :30; Mobius category: 54; Mobius identifier: XT643-54-U-89-U, 1989 September 25; 86
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0148)
  - Chicagoland Cadillac Dealers, "Smart Money #1/Future Value" :30, "Smart Money #2/Dollar Decline" :30, "Smart Money #4/Trade Deficit" :30, Eisaman, Johns & Laws; Mobius category: 2; Mobius identifier: XT1097ABC-2-U-89-U, 1989 September 27; 87
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0127)
  - Chicagoland Chevy Dealers/NW Ind. Dealers, "The Lift/Mechanic/Rev. 2" :30, Eisaman, Johns & Laws; Mobius category: 2; Mobius identifier: XT1088-2-U-89-U, 1989 September 27; 88
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0128)
  - WLUP FM Radio, "Rock 'N Roll Preacher", "Subway", Eisaman, Johns & Laws; Mobius category: 81; Mobius identifier: XT1078AB-81-U-89-U, 1989 September 27; 89
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0130)
  - Banks of Iowa, "Economic Development" :30, "Values" :30, "Leaving Home" :30; Mobius category: 69; Mobius identifier: XT409ABC-69-U-89-U, 1989 September 27; 90
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0136)
  - WLUP FM Radio, "Subway", Eisaman, Johns & Laws; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT1095AB-73-U-89-U, 1989 September 27; 91
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0154)
  - WLUP FM Radio, "Rock 'N Roll Preacher", :30, Eisaman, Johns & Laws; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT1094-73-U-89-U, 1989 September 27; 92
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0155)
  - WLUP FM Radio, "Subway", Eisaman, Johns & Laws; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT1004-73-U-89-U, 1989 September 27; 93
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0156)
  - Police Story Spot, :30; Mobius category: 80; Mobius identifier: XT823-80-U-89-U, 1989 September 28; 94
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0118)
  - Reebok, ERS Sports Conditioning; Mobius category: 12; Mobius identifier: XT1011-12-U-89-U, 1989 September 28; 95
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0126)
  - Kiro Newsradio "Traffic Blues"; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT1300-73-U-89-U, 1989 September 28; 96
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0144)
  - Police Story Spot, :30; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT818-73-U-89-U, 1989 September 28; 97
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0152)
  - Wardair, "London", "Paris", "Amsterdam"; Mobius category: 62; Mobius identifier: XT903ABC-62-0-89-C, 1989 September 29; 98
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0055)
  - Pied-8877, "Travel More", McKinney & Silver; Mobius category: 62; Mobius identifier: XT1352-62-0-89-U, 1989 September 29; 99
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0064)
  - Norw-8912, "Broadway" Agency Ver.; Mobius category: 62; Mobius identifier: XT1354-62-0-89-U, 1989 September 29; 100
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0065)
  - Publicite Martin, Canada Post Corporation, Priority Courier, Awareness/Trace, :15; Mobius category: 62; Mobius identifier: XT924-62-0-89-C, 1989 September 29; 101
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0067)
  - Publicite Martin, Canada Post Corporation, 1) Awareness/Late, :15, 2) Awareness/EMS, :15, 3) Awareness/Weekend, :15; Mobius category: 62; Mobius identifier: XT920ABC-62-0-89-C, 1989 September 29; 102
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0068)
  - McCann Erickson, Alka Seltzer, "It Isn't Alka Seltzer" :15; Mobius category: 81; Mobius identifier: XT1149-81-0-89-U, 1989 September 29; 103
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0084)
  - W.B. Donner, Arby's, "Burger Alert" :30; Mobius category:; Mobius identifier:, 1989 September 29; 104
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0085)
  - CME, Tampax, "Metamorphosis" :15; Mobius category: 43; Mobius identifier: XT1146-43-0-89-U, 1989 September 29; 105
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0086)
  - CME, Tampax, "Metamorphosis" :15; Mobius category: 87; Mobius identifier: XT1145-87-0-89-U, 1989 September 29; 106
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0087)
  - W.B. Donner, Arby's, "Burger Alert" :30; Mobius category: 83; Mobius identifier: XT1143-83-0-89-U, 1989 September 29; 107
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 108, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0088)
  - ABC News Promos, "Prime Time Live" Premiere Promos; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT1181ABC-73-U-89-U, 1989 September 29; 108
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0149)
  - ABC News Promos, Show Closes; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT1178ABC-73-U-89-U, 1989 September 29; 109
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0150)
  - Quotes, War & Remembrance, :30; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT824-73-U-89-U, 1989 September 29; 110
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0151)
  - Geo/Getting To Know You (Full-Line) :60; Mobius category: 82; Mobius identifier: XT1280-82-0-89-U, 1989 October 02; 111
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0100)
  - More New-Truck :30; Mobius category: 82; Mobius identifier: XT1245-82-0-89-U, 1989 October 02; 112
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0101)
  - More New-Van :30; Mobius category: 82; Mobius identifier: XT1266-82-0-89-U, 1989 October 02; 113
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0102)
  - Heartbeat News :60; Mobius category: 79; Mobius identifier: XT1271-79-0-89-U, 1989 October 02; 114
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0103)
  - Geo/Getting To Know You (Full-Line) :60; Mobius category: 79; Mobius identifier: XT1269-79-0-89-U, 1989 October 02; 115
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0104)
  - More New-Van :30; Mobius category: 79; Mobius identifier: XT1264-79-0-89-U, 1989 October 02; 116
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0105)
  - More New-Truck :30; Mobius category: 79; Mobius identifier: XT1253-79-0-89-U, 1989 October 02; 117
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0106)
  - Something Different (Lumina/APV) :30; Mobius category: 79; Mobius identifier: XT1248-79-0-89-U, 1989 October 02; 118
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0107)
  - Jordan Tamraz & Caruso, Chicagoland Buick Dealers, "Regal Print-Out"; Mobius category: 2; Mobius identifier: XT1191-2-U-89-U, 1989 October 02; 119
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0121)
  - Jordan Tamraz & Caruso, Chicagoland Buick Dealers, "Rip-Revised"; Mobius category: 2; Mobius identifier: XT1190-2-U-89-U, 1989 October 02; 120
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0122)
  - Jordan Tamraz & Caruso, Chicagoland Buick, "Electra Fact / 2.9 / 1500" :30, "Best $3000" :30, "Regal Fact / 2.9 / 1000"; Mobius category: 2; Mobius identifier: XT1188ABC-2-U-89-U, 1989 October 02; 121
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0123)
  - Charlex Mandee "Denim Jeans & Tops"; Mobius category: 11; Mobius identifier: XT1619-11-U-89-U, 1989 October 11; 122
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0134)
  - Charles Campbell - An Eye For An Eye, Steve Amlley & Chris Raaum - Producers; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT684-73-U-89-U, circa 1989; 123
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 32, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0002)
  - Kodak/Film, "Worlds Greatest Pictures"; Mobius category: 44; Mobius identifier: XT899-44-0-89-U, circa 1989; 124
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0054)
  - GSD&M Advertising, :15, "Cab Driver", 62 Over $10,000; Mobius category: 62; Mobius identifier: XT775-62-0-89-U, circa 1989; 125
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0056)
  - GSD&M Advertising, :30, "Stop in Your Tracks", 62 Over $10,000; Mobius category: 62; Mobius identifier: XT777-62-0-89-U, circa 1989; 126
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0057)
  - Businessman, GSD&M Advertising, 62 Over $10,000; Mobius category: 62; Mobius identifier: XT774-62-0-89-U, circa 1989; 127
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0066)
  - Detroit City Airport, :60, 62 Over $10,000; Mobius category: 62; Mobius identifier: XT778-62-0-89-U, circa 1989; 128
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0069)
  - Peanuts :15, 62 Over $10,000; Mobius category: 62; Mobius identifier: XT772-62-0-89-U, circa 1989; 129
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0070)
  - Kodak/Film, "True Joy" :45, "Daddy's Little Girl" :60,; Mobius category: 44; Mobius identifier: XT877AB-44-0-89-U, circa 1989; 130
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 107, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0071)
  - Ron Foth Advertising, Elder Beerman "Shop!" Category #11; Mobius category: 11; Mobius identifier: XT392-11-0-89-U, circa 1989; 131
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0089)
  - J. Walter Thompson, Kodak/Film, Daddy's Little Girl; Mobius category: 44; Mobius identifier: XT868-44-0-89-U, circa 1989; 132
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0090)
  - J. Walter Thompson, Bell Atlantic, "Centrex" :30, "Pickle" :30, "Schmidt" :30; Mobius category: 59; Mobius identifier: XT892ABC-59-0-89-U, circa 1989; 133
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0091)
  - J. Walter Thompson, Kodak/Film, "True Joy" :45; Mobius category: 44; Mobius identifier: XT893-44-0-89-U, circa 1989; 134
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0092)
  - J. Walter Thompson, Bell Atlantic, "Walnut" :30, "Thin Ice" :30, "Butterfly" :30; Mobius category: 59; Mobius identifier: XT891ABC-59-0-89-U, circa 1989; 135
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0093)
  - J. Walter Thompson, Bell Atlantic, "Money" :30; Mobius category: 59; Mobius identifier: XT890-59-0-89-U, circa 1989; 136
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0094)
  - Customer Service 1003 B :30, 1003 C :30, 1003 D :30; Mobius category: 59; Mobius identifier: XT29ABC-59-0-89-U, circa 1989; 137
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0095)
  - J. Walter Thompson, Bell Atlantic, "Schmidt" :30; Mobius category: 59; Mobius identifier: XT874-59-0-89-U, circa 1989; 138
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0096)
  - J. Walter Thompson, "Centrex" :30; Mobius category: 59; Mobius identifier: XT875-59-0-89-U, circa 1989; 139
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0097)
  - 88 Films, Weichart Realtors "Baby Booklet" :30; Mobius category: 60; Mobius identifier: XT655-60-0-89-U, circa 1989; 140
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0098)
  - The Animation House, Eggo Waffles, "Pepperoni Peanut Butter" :30; Mobius category: 77; Mobius identifier: XT1473-77-0-89-C, circa 1989; 141
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0099)
  - Dressin' Up :30, Client: Polar Trading Co., Category 82, Polar Beer, PB-255A, Gold Coast Adv.; Mobius category: 82; Mobius identifier: XT1562-82-0-89-U, circa 1989; 142
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 136, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0109)
  - Get Ready, Waterloo Greyhound Park, :30, Category #49; Mobius category: 49; Mobius identifier: XT577-49-U-89-U, circa 1989; 143
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0120)
  - Grabpa, :30, "Something Different-Music"; Mobius category: 49; Mobius identifier: XT711-49-U-89-U, circa 1989; 144
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 138, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0125)
  - Agency: Cramer Krasselt, Client: Valley Toyota Dealers, Title: "Quality Clearance Sale" :30; Mobius category: 2; Mobius identifier: XT363-2-U-89-U, circa 1989; 145
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0129)
  - Massachusetts Commission Against Discrimination, "Guilty" :30; Mobius category: 80; Mobius identifier: XT435-80-U-89-U, circa 1989; 146
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0131)
  - Holmes :60, Mission Impossible :45, Jethrow & Co :60; Mobius category: 12; Mobius identifier: XT1298ABC-12-U-89-C, circa 1989; 147
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0135)
  - Client: Fireside Dodge, Title: Spaghetti Western, :60; Mobius category: 2; Mobius identifier: XT398-2-U-89-U, circa 1989; 148
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 139, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0138)
  - News-Fernando Escandon; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT1046-73-U-89-U, circa 1989; 149
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0142)
  - KLZX (Z93) Radio, "Where's Jon and Dan?" :15, :30; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT1398AB-73-U-89-U, circa 1989; 150
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0143)
  - Esleep Commercial, :30; Mobius category: 10; Mobius identifier: XT340-10A-U-89-U, circa 1989; 151
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0145)
  - Maximilian Wrinkle Cream, Direct Response, 120 sec.; Mobius category: 43; Mobius identifier: XT1174-43-U-89-U, circa 1989; 152
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0146)
  - Diamond Essence/Woman's Best Friend Direct Response, 120 sec.; Mobius category: 44; Mobius identifier: XT1173-44-U-89-U, circa 1989; 153
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0147)
  - KABC-TV - News Open, :30; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT1388-73-U-89-U, circa 1989; 154
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0153)
  - Client: Modesto Police Dept., Title: Help Stop Crime, :60; Mobius category: 73; Mobius identifier: XT397-73-U-89-U, circa 1989; 155
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 140, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0157)
  - Some Like It Hot, Eastern Airlines; Mobius category: 84; Mobius identifier: XT603-84-0-89-U, 1990; 156
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 32, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0004)
  - Sears - Discover Card, "Dawn General", Dawn Savings", "Dawn Dividends", J. Walter Thompson, undated; 157
    - Original Umatic videocassette (Box 32, Video-cassette RL00902-UM-0005)